Africana Center Records UA113
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Africana Center Records
1939 -- 2012
1970 -- 2005
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Africana Center
UA113
13.64 Linear Feet 7 record cartons, 3 document boxes, 2 oversized boxes
5 Digital Object(s) 5 digital objects containing 30 files.
220.086 Megabytes
This collections contains the records of the Africana Center, founded at Tufts University in 1969 to address the needs and concerns of students of African descent. Records include subject files, artifacts, photographs, and publications.
Arrangement
This collection is organized in four series: Artifacts and posters; Photographs and slides; Publications; and Subject files.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of records from the Africana Center. It contains artifacts; photographs; publications; and subject files collected and created by the Africana Center from 1969 to 2012. Materials within the subject files date from 1939-2011. The majority of the collection dates from 1970 – 2005. The material was created or used in the day to day functions of the Africana Center and mainly consists of paper records in the form of subject files.
The artifacts in this collection include banners created by students for Africana Center events, as well as posters, a t-shirt, and buttons and a flag commemorating Martin Luther King, Jr. Photographs in this collection mainly record Africana Center events. Publications and subject files include many formats and cover a wide range of topics, including affirmative action, the Tufts Black Alumni Association, freshmen orientation, student life, Black History month, and guest speakers and performers.
The records relate to the Center's work to enhance the academic mission of the University by ensuring that students of African descent have access to resources supporting a successful Tufts experience and preparing them for leadership positions. The collection covers the Center's work from its founding in 1969 through to its development into a provider of academic and social resources and activities for students of African descent. Some of the larger projects represented in the records include the founding of the Tufts Black Alumni Association; the organization of the freshmen orientation Cape Cod retreat; the development of the Black Student Handbook; the development of the peer advisor program; Black History month events; and the administration of Capen House, a living and learning space for fifteen undergraduates interested in African diaspora history and culture who reside in the house, which is located on the second and third floors of the Africana Center building.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1969, the Africana Center was developed in recognition of the realities of the needs and concerns of the students of African descent on a predominately white campus. The Center works to enhance the academic mission of the university by ensuring that students of African descent have access to a variety of academic, cultural and student resources that encourages them to have a successful Tufts experience and prepares them to be leaders for a wide range of professional experiences. In addition, the Center works to ensure that students have access to all necessary resources, advises the administrative and academic offices of the university on such issues and advocates proactively for students. The Africana Center is located at 8 Professors Row on the 1st Floor. The second and third floors of the building serve as a living and learning space (Capen House) for fifteen undergraduates who reside in the house during the academic year. These students are selected each year to live in the dorm and work as a community to complete individual and group projects which celebrate the rich cultural heritage of people of African descent.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Separated Materials
Duplicative copies of the publication Onyx were transferred to UP034.
Student life; African American college students; African American college teachers; Affirmative action programs in education; African American History Month; Student Affairs and Services; Student life; Student activities; Student activism; Admissions and Recruitment; Curriculum and Instruction -- Scholarships, Fellowships, Awards; Africana Center; Office of Equal Opportunity and Affirmative Action; Hill Collins, Patricia
- Artifacts and posters, circa 1980 -- 2012; UA113.001; 4.41 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object containing 2 files.; 219 Megabytes
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Arrangement
  Arrangement reflects the physical order of items.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains banners, posters, buttons, flags, and a t-shirt, all created and collected by the Africana Center. The banners and posters document events sponsored by the Africana Center in the 1980s and 1990s. There is also a digitized banner for the 30th anniversary of the Africana Center in 1999. The buttons and flags were created for Martin Luther King Jr. remembrance events.
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Scholarship Fund flags, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.001.001.00001; 2 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_79d2a348dd3856980f40372a0c63f258, Object 1-2, Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - Tufts Remembers Dr. Martin Luther King buttons, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.001.001.00002; 2 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_79d2a348dd3856980f40372a0c63f258, Object 3-4, Box 1)
  - Africana Center t-shirt, circa 1990 -- 2012; UA113.001.001.00003; 1 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_79d2a348dd3856980f40372a0c63f258, Object 5, Box 1)
  - Caribbean Club Weekend banner, 1987; UA113.001.001.00004; 1 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_79d2a348dd3856980f40372a0c63f258, Object 6, Box 1)
  - Beauty of Color banner, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.001.001.00005; 1 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_79d2a348dd3856980f40372a0c63f258, Object 7, Box 1)
  - Looking Black on Ourselves banner, circa 1995 -- 1998; UA113.001.001.00006; 1 Artifact(s) (Box data_value_missing_3381867982ba6d0371864bebb21bc86c, Object 8, Box 1)
  - Black History Month at Tufts poster, 2012; UA113.001.002.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_3a9ab5f0bc2e8380e9400e95783a205a, Folder 1, Box 2)
  - Black History Month poster, 1980; UA113.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_3a9ab5f0bc2e8380e9400e95783a205a, Folder 2, Box 2)
  - Event posters, circa 1989 -- 1998; UA113.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_3a9ab5f0bc2e8380e9400e95783a205a, Folder 3, Box 2)
  - 30th Anniversary poster, 1999; UA113.001.00001
- Photographs and slides, circa 1970 -- 2005; UA113.002; 1.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  This series contains photographs, slides, and negatives created and compiled by the Africana Center circa 1970 to circa 2005. The subjects of the photographs include events, student life, and a few portraits of visiting speakers such as Sonia Sanchez and Manning Marable. Some events featured in the collection are the pre-freshman orientation at Cape Cod, graduation, award ceremonies, Kwanzaa dinners, fashion shows, sports events, and music and dance performances.
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod photographs, circa 1994 -- 2001; UA113.002.003.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 1, Box 3)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod photographs, circa 1996; UA113.002.003.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 2, Box 3)
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod photographs, circa 1997; UA113.002.003.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 3, Box 3)
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod photographs and negatives, circa 1996; UA113.002.003.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 4, Box 3)
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod photographs and negatives, circa 1990 -- 2000; UA113.002.003.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 5-6, Box 3)
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod and Kwanzaa photographs, circa 1994 -- 2001; UA113.002.003.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 7-8, Box 3)
  - African American Center freshman orientation at Cape Cod and Kwanzaa photographs and negatives, circa 1996 -- 2001; UA113.002.003.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 9, Box 3)
  - Africana Center scrapbook photo album - folder 1 of 2, circa 1970 -- 1991; UA113.002.003.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 10, Box 3)
  - Africana Center scrapbook photo album - folder 2 of 2, circa 1970 -- 1991; UA113.002.003.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 11, Box 3)
  - Africana Center scrapbook photo album, circa 1970 -- 1992; UA113.002.003.00010; 6 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 12-17, Box 3)
  - Africana House photo album, circa 1980 -- 1990; UA113.002.003.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 18, Box 3)
  - Award ceremony and graduation photographs and negatives, 1998; UA113.002.003.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 19, Box 3)
  - Award photographs and negatives, circa 1995 -- 2005; UA113.002.003.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 20, Box 3)
  - Dance photographs and Africana Center negatives, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.002.003.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 21, Box 3)
  - Event photographs, circa 1995; UA113.002.003.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 22, Box 3)
  - Event slides, circa 1975 -- 1990; UA113.002.003.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 23, Box 3)
  - Event slides, circa 1977 -- 1981; UA113.002.003.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 24, Box 3)
  - Fashion show photographs and negatives, circa 1980 -- 1999; UA113.002.003.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 25, Box 3)
  - Group portrait, circa 1980 -- 1990; UA113.002.003.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 26, Box 3)
  - Graduation negatives, circa 1999; UA113.002.003.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 27, Box 3)
  - Graduation photographs, circa 1999; UA113.002.003.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 28, Box 3)
  - Graduation photographs, 2000; UA113.002.003.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 29, Box 3)
  - Jazz Workshop #1 photographs and negatives, circa 1980 -- 1995; UA113.002.003.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 30, Box 3)
  - Negatives, circa 1980 -- 2000; UA113.002.003.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 31-32, Box 3)
  - Negatives, circa 1996; UA113.002.003.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 33, Box 3)
  - Photographs, circa 1996; UA113.002.003.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_f0c1d3f953ed958541f3238f09a526db, Folder 34, Box 3)
  - Photographs, circa 1997; UA113.002.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 1, Box 4)
  - Photographs and envelope, circa 1978 -- 1987; UA113.002.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 2, Box 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, circa 1978 -- 2001; UA113.002.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 3, Box 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, circa 1997; UA113.002.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 4, Box 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, circa 1999; UA113.002.004.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 5, Box 4)
  - Sanchez, Sonia, circa 1975 -- 1985; UA113.002.004.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 6, Box 4)
  - Slides, circa 1995 -- 2005; UA113.002.004.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 7, Box 4)
  - Sports, dance, and student life photographs, circa 1953 -- 1990; UA113.002.004.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 8, Box 4)
  - Student life photographs and negatives, circa 1999; UA113.002.004.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 9, Box 4)
  - Winners of the Tufts Arts and Sciences Faculty/Staff Multicultural Service Award, 2000; UA113.002.004.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 10, Box 4)
- Publications, 1973 -- 2012; UA113.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contain publications created or collected by the African Center, including periodicals, newsletters, pamphlets, and handbooks published by the Center, by student groups at Tufts, and by Tufts University. There are also professional association newsletters and periodicals. Subjects covered by the publications vary widely and include affirmative action, Black History Month, African American art, and minority student life.
  - Administrator, 1986 -- 1987; UA113.003.004.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 11, Box 4)
  - Affirmation Action Register, 1986; UA113.003.004.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 12, Box 4)
  - African American Center Newsletter Fall/Winter, 1985; UA113.003.004.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 13, Box 4)
  - African American Center Study Guide, circa 1996 -- 2000; UA113.003.004.00014; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 14-16, Box 4)
  - BiblioTech Connections, 1999; UA113.003.004.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 17, Box 4)
  - Black History Month 2006, UA113.003.004.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 18, Box 4)
  - Black People and the Constitution, 1983; UA113.003.004.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 19, Box 4)
  - Black Student Handbook, 1979 -- 1994; UA113.003.004.00018; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 20-22, Box 4)
  - Boston Globe, 1987; UA113.003.004.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 23, Box 4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.003.004.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 24, Box 4)
  - Career Services Guide for Tufts Students & Alumni, 1999 -- 2000; UA113.003.004.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 25, Box 4)
  - Collegiate Web Tufts University, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.003.004.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 26, Box 4)
  - Commencement program, 1994 -- 1998; UA113.003.004.00023; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 27-28, Box 4)
  - Expressions, 1987; UA113.003.004.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 29, Box 4)
  - Habitats, 1994 -- 1995; UA113.003.004.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 30, Box 4)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1986 -- 1987; UA113.003.004.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 31, Box 4)
  - Lincoln Filene Center report, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.003.004.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 32, Box 4)
  - Newsletter, Academic and Career Enrichment Services, 1986 -- 1987; UA113.003.004.00028; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 33-35, Box 4)
  - Onyx, 1989 -- 2009; UA113.003.004.00029; 5 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 36-40, Box 4)
  - Pamphlets, circa 1997 -- 2004; UA113.003.004.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 41, Box 4)
  - Programs, study guides, and publications, 1983 -- 2012; UA113.003.004.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 42, Box 4)
  - Publications, 1983 -- 1985; UA113.003.004.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 43, Box 4)
  - State of Black Boston Executive Summary, 2011; UA113.003.004.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 44, Box 4)
  - Tufts Bulletin, 1994; UA113.003.004.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 45, Box 4)
  - Tufts Community Union Senate Treasury Procedures Manual, 2002 -- 2003; UA113.003.004.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 46, Box 4)
  - Tufts Diversity and Excellence: Together We Can Make a Difference, circa 1988 -- 1999; UA113.003.004.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 47, Box 4)
  - Tufts Graduate and Professional Studies, 2000 -- 2001; UA113.003.004.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 48, Box 4)
  - Tufts Polices for Social Functions, 1988; UA113.003.004.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_35877a21eaf66fde257cac570cfbdcfc, Folder 49, Box 4)
  - Tufts publications, 1994 -- 2003; UA113.003.005.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 1-2, Box 5)
  - Tufts University Business Conduct Policy, 1996; UA113.003.005.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 3, Box 5)
  - Tufts University Engineering News, 1986 -- 1987; UA113.003.005.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 4, Box 5)
  - Tufts University International Newsletter, 1986; UA113.003.005.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 5, Box 5)
  - Tufts University Newsletter, 1987; UA113.003.005.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 6, Box 5)
  - Tufts University Summer Session, 2000; UA113.003.005.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 7, Box 5)
- Subject files, circa 1939 -- 2011; UA113.004; 6.64 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s) 4 digital objects containing 28 files.; 1.086 Megabytes
  This series contains subject files compiled by the Africana Center and encompassing many formats, including administrative documents and office files that include financial, personnel, and event documentation; clippings; photographs; correspondence; memos; mailing lists; and reports. Topics of particular note in the subject files include affirmative action; the Black Alumni Association; Black History Month; Capen House, a living and learning space for undergraduates interested in African diaspora history and culture; and student orientation and peer advising.
  - Academic reports, 1995; UA113.004.005.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 8, Box 5)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - Administrative actions, 1994; UA113.004.005.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 9, Box 5)
  - Affirmative Action Forum, 1996; UA113.004.005.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 10, Box 5)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1991 -- 1997; UA113.004.005.00010; 6 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 11-16, Box 5)
    Missing 1993.
  - African American Center advisory committee, 1996; UA113.004.005.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 17, Box 5)
  - African American Center annual report, 1992 -- 1993; UA113.004.005.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 18, Box 5)
  - African American Center, Asian American Center, and Hispanic Center cookout, 1994; UA113.004.005.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 19, Box 5)
  - African American Center Certificate of Academic Excellence, 2000; UA113.004.005.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 20, Box 5)
  - African American Center orientation response forms, 1997; UA113.004.005.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 21, Box 5)
  - Africa and New World Staff, circa 1996 -- 2000; UA113.004.005.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 22, Box 5)
  - After hours staff and protocols, 1998 -- 1999; UA113.004.005.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 23, Box 5)
  - Alpha Rho Lambda budget, circa 1999; UA113.004.005.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 24, Box 5)
  - Algebra project, circa 1992 -- 1993; UA113.004.005.00019; 2 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 25-26, Box 5)
  - Algebra project photo requests, 1993; UA113.004.005.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 27, Box 5)
  - Ambassadors, 1999; UA113.004.005.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 28, Box 5)
  - American Anthropological Association, 2000; UA113.004.005.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 29, Box 5)
  - American Program Bureau, circa 1979 -- 1980; UA113.004.005.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 30, Box 5)
  - American Student Assistance monthly bulletin, 1993 -- 1994; UA113.004.005.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 31, Box 5)
  - Annual space inventory info, 1992 -- 1998; UA113.004.005.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 32, Box 5)
  - Application for use of facilities, 1999; UA113.004.005.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 33, Box 5)
  - Art of Black Dance, circa 2000 -- 2001; UA113.004.005.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 34, Box 5)
  - Art of Black Dance and Music, Inc., 1989; UA113.004.005.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 35, Box 5)
  - Association for Black Cultural Centers, 1988 -- 1999; UA113.004.005.00029; 3 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 36-38, Box 5)
  - Awards banquet, 1978; UA113.004.005.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box data_value_missing_1282a5f67dd7a667177a917127b6a4f6, Folder 39, Box 5)